{
  "Admin": {
    "access": "Access:",
    "access0": "None",
    "access1": "Moderator",
    "access2": "Admin",
    "ban": "Ban",
    "bancaption": "Ban {00}",
    "banprompt": "Banning {00} will not allow them to access this game for the duration you set!",
    "chronological": "123...",
    "chronologicaltip": "Order maps chronologically.",
    "face": "Face:",
    "kick": "Kick",
    "kill": "Kill",
    "maplist": "Map List:",
    "mute": "Mute",
    "mutecaption": "Mute {00}",
    "muteprompt": "Muting {00} will not allow them to chat in game for the duration you set!",
    "name": "Name:",
    "noclip": "No Clip:",
    "nocliptip": "Check to walk through obstacles.",
    "none": "None",
    "setface": "Set Face",
    "setpower": "Set Power",
    "setsprite": "Set Sprite",
    "sprite": "Sprite:",
    "title": "Administration",
    "unban": "Unban",
    "unbancaption": "Unban {00}",
    "unbanprompt": "Are you sure that you want to unban {00}?",
    "unmute": "Unmute",
    "unmutecaption": "Unute {00}",
    "unmuteprompt": "Are you sure that you want to unmute {00}?",
    "warp2me": "Warp To Me",
    "warpme2": "Warp Me To"
  },
  "Bags": {
    "retreiveitem": "Retreive Item",
    "retreiveitemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to retreive?",
    "storeitem": "Store Item",
    "storeitemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to store?",
    "title": "Bag"
  },
  "Bank": {
    "deposititem": "Deposit Item",
    "deposititemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to deposit?",
    "title": "Bank",
    "withdrawitem": "Withdraw Item",
    "withdrawitemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to withdraw?"
  },
  "BanMute": {
    "oneday": "1 day",
    "onemonth": "1 month",
    "oneweek": "1 week",
    "oneyear": "1 year",
    "twodays": "2 days",
    "twomonths": "2 months",
    "twoweeks": "2 weeks",
    "threedays": "3 days",
    "fourdays": "4 days",
    "fivedays": "5 days",
    "sixmonths": "6 months",
    "cancel": "Cancel:",
    "duration": "Duration:",
    "forever": "Indefinitely",
    "ip": "Include IP:",
    "ok": "Okay:",
    "reason": "Reason:"
  },
  "Character": {
    "equipment": "Equipment:",
    "levelandclass": "Level: {00} {01}",
    "name": "{00}",
    "points": "Points: {00}",
    "stat0": "{00}: {01}",
    "stat1": "{00}: {01}",
    "stat2": "{00}: {01}",
    "stat3": "{00}: {01}",
    "stat4": "{00}: {01}",
    "stats": "Stats:",
    "title": "Character"
  },
  "CharacterCreation": {
    "back": "Back",
    "class": "Class:",
    "create": "Create",
    "female": "Female",
    "gender": "Gender:",
    "hint": "Customize",
    "hint2": "Your Character",
    "invalidname": "Character name is invalid. Please use alphanumeric characters with a length between 2 and 20.",
    "male": "Male",
    "name": "Char Name:",
    "title": "Create Character"
  },
  "CharacterSelection": {
    "delete": "Delete",
    "deleteprompt": "Are you sure you want to delete {00}? This action is irreversible!",
    "deletetitle": "Delete {00}",
    "empty": "Empty Character Slot",
    "info": "Level {00} {01}",
    "logout": "Logout",
    "name": "{00}",
    "new": "New",
    "play": "Use",
    "title": "Select a Character"
  },
  "Chatbox": {
    "channel": "Channel:",
    "channels": {
      "0": "local",
      "1": "global",
      "2": "party"
    },
    "channeladmin": "admin",
    "enterchat": "Click here to chat.",
    "enterchat1": "Press {00} to chat.",
    "enterchat2": "Press {00} or {01} to chat.",
    "send": "Send",
    "title": "Chat",
    "toofast": "You are chatting too fast!"
  },
  "Colors": {
    "presets": {
      "0": "Black",
      "1": "White",
      "2": "Pink",
      "3": "Blue",
      "4": "Red",
      "5": "Green",
      "6": "Yellow",
      "7": "Orange",
      "8": "Purple",
      "9": "Gray",
      "10": "Cyan"
    }
  },
  "Combat": {
    "exp": "Experience",
    "stat0": "Attack",
    "stat1": "Ability Power",
    "stat2": "Defense",
    "stat3": "Magic Resist",
    "stat4": "Speed",
    "targetoutsiderange": "Target too far away!",
    "vital0": "Health",
    "vital1": "Mana",
    "warningtitle": "Combat Warning!",
    "warningforceclose": "Game was closed while in combat! Your character will remain logged in until combat has concluded!",
    "warninglogout": "You are about to logout while in combat! Your character will remain in-game until combat has ended! Are you sure you want to logout now?",
    "warningcharacterselect": "You are about to logout while in combat! Your character will remain in-game until combat has ended! Are you sure you want to logout now?",
    "warningexitdesktop": "You are about to exit while in combat! Your character will remain in-game until combat has ended! Are you sure you want to quit now?"
  },
  "Controls": {
    "controldict": {
      "attackinteract": "Attack/Interact:",
      "block": "Block:",
      "autotarget": "Auto Target:",
      "enter": "Enter:",
      "hotkey0": "Hot Key 0:",
      "hotkey1": "Hot Key 1:",
      "hotkey2": "Hot Key 2:",
      "hotkey3": "Hot Key 3:",
      "hotkey4": "Hot Key 4:",
      "hotkey5": "Hot Key 5:",
      "hotkey6": "Hot Key 6:",
      "hotkey7": "Hot Key 7:",
      "hotkey8": "Hot Key 8:",
      "hotkey9": "Hot Key 9:",
      "movedown": "Down:",
      "moveleft": "Left:",
      "moveright": "Right:",
      "moveup": "Up:",
      "pickup": "Pick Up:",
      "screenshot": "Screenshot:",
      "openmenu": "Open Menu:",
      "openinventory": "Open Inventory:",
      "openquests": "Open Quests:",
      "opencharacterinfo": "Open Character Info:",
      "openparties": "Open Parties:",
      "openspells": "Open Spells:",
      "openfriends": "Open Friends:",
      "opensettings": "Open Settings:",
      "opendebugger": "Open Debugger:",
      "openadminpanel": "Open Admin Panel:",
      "togglegui": "Toggle Interface:"
    },
    "edit": "Edit Controls",
    "listening": "Listening",
    "title": "Controls"
  },
  "Crafting": {
    "craft": "Craft",
    "incorrectresources": "You do not have the correct resources to craft this item.",
    "ingredients": "Requires:",
    "product": "Crafting:",
    "recipes": "Recipes:",
    "title": "Crafting Table"
  },
  "Credits": {
    "back": "Main Menu",
    "title": "Credits"
  },
  "Debug": {
    "draws": "Draws: {00}",
    "entitiesdrawn": "Entities Drawn: {00}",
    "fps": "FPS: {00}",
    "knownentities": "Known Entities: {00}",
    "knownmaps": "Known Maps: {00}",
    "lightsdrawn": "Lights Drawn: {00}",
    "map": "Map: {00}",
    "mapsdrawn": "Maps Drawn: {00}",
    "ping": "Ping: {00}",
    "time": "Time: {00}",
    "title": "Debug",
    "x": "X: {00}",
    "y": "Y: {00}",
    "z": "Z: {00}"
  },
  "EntityBox": {
    "nameandlevel": "{00}    {01}",
    "cooldown": "{00}s",
    "exp": "EXP:",
    "expval": "{00} / {01}",
    "friend": "Befriend",
    "friendtip": "Send {00} a friend request.",
    "level": "Lv. {00}",
    "map": "{00}",
    "maxlevel": "Max Level",
    "party": "Party",
    "partytip": "Invite {00} to your party.",
    "trade": "Trade",
    "tradetip": "Request to trade with {00}.",
    "vital0": "HP:",
    "vital0val": "{00} / {01}",
    "vital1": "MP:",
    "vital1val": "{00} / {01}"
  },
  "Errors": {
    "displaynotsupported": "Invalid Display Configuration!",
    "displaynotsupportederror": "Fullscreen {00} resolution is not supported on this device!",
    "errorencountered": "The Intersect Client has encountered an error and must close. Error information can be found in logs/errors.log",
    "notconnected": "Not connected to the game server. Is it online?",
    "notsupported": "Not Supported!",
    "openalerror": "OpenAL Initialization Error! Try updating your audio drivers! Make sure you have speakers available and enabled. Maybe try plugging in headphones. Visit {00} (may open automatically) for more information.",
    "openallink": "https://goo.gl/Nbx6hx",
    "openglerror": "OpenGL Initialization Error! Try updating your graphics drivers! Make sure you're not using remote desktop software. Visit {00} (may open automatically) for more information.",
    "opengllink": "https://goo.gl/RSP3ts",
    "passwordinvalid": "Password is invalid. Please use alphanumeric characters with a length between 4 and 20.",
    "resourcesnotfound": "The resources directory could not be found! Intersect will now close.",
    "resourcesnotfoundtitle": "Resources not found!",
    "title": "Error!",
    "usernameinvalid": "Username is invalid. Please use alphanumeric characters with a length between 2 and 20.",
    "loadfile": "Failed to load a {00}. Please send the game administrator a copy of your errors log file in the logs directory.",
    "lostconnection": "Lost connection to the game server. Please make sure you're connected to the internet and try again!"
  },
  "Words": {
    "lcase_sound": "sound",
    "lcase_music": "soundtrack",
    "lcase_sprite": "sprite",
    "lcase_animation": "animation"
  },
  "EventWindow": {
    "continue": "Continue"
  },
  "ForgotPass": {
    "back": "Back",
    "hint": "If your account exists we will send you a temporary password reset code.",
    "label": "Enter your username or email below:",
    "submit": "Submit",
    "title": "Password Reset"
  },
  "Friends": {
    "addfriend": "Add Friend",
    "addfriendtitle": "Add Friend",
    "addfriendprompt": "Who would you like to add as a friend?",
    "removefriend": "Remove Friend",
    "removefriendprompt": "Do you wish to remove {00} from your friends list?",
    "request": "Friend Request",
    "requestprompt": "{00} has sent you a friend request. Do you accept?",
    "title": "Friends"
  },
  "GameMenu": {
    "character": "Character Info",
    "menu": "Open Menu",
    "friends": "Friends",
    "items": "Inventory",
    "party": "Party",
    "quest": "Quest Log",
    "spells": "Spell Book"
  },
  "General": {
    "none": "None"
  },
  "InputBox": {
    "cancel": "Cancel",
    "no": "No",
    "okay": "Okay",
    "yes": "Yes"
  },
  "Inventory": {
    "cooldown": "{00}s",
    "dropitem": "Drop Item",
    "dropitemprompt": "How many/much {00} do you want to drop?",
    "dropprompt": "Do you wish to drop the item: {00}?",
    "equippedicon": "E",
    "title": "Inventory"
  },
  "ItemDesc": {
    "bonuses": "Stat Bonuses:",
    "damage": "Base Damage: {00}",
    "desc": "{00}",
    "effect": "Bonus Effect: {00}% {01}",
    "effects": {
      "0": "Cooldown Reduction",
      "1": "Lifesteal",
      "2": "Tenacity",
      "3": "Luck",
      "4": "Exp Increase"
    },
    "itemtypes": {
      "0": "None",
      "1": "Equipment",
      "2": "Consumable",
      "3": "Currency",
      "4": "Spell",
      "5": "Special",
      "6": "Bag"
    },
    "prereq": "Prerequisites:",
    "stats": {
      "0": "Attack: {00}",
      "1": "Ability Power: {00}",
      "2": "Defense: {00}",
      "3": "Magic Resist: {00}",
      "4": "Speed: {00}"
    },
    "twohand": "2H",
    "rarity": {
      "0": "None",
      "1": "Common",
      "2": "Uncommon",
      "3": "Rare",
      "4": "Epic",
      "5": "Legendary"
    },
    "vitals": {
      "0": "HP: {00}",
      "1": "MP: {00}"
    }
  },
  "Keys": {
    "keydict": {
      "a": "A",
      "add": "Add",
      "alt": "Alt",
      "apps": "Apps",
      "attn": "Attn",
      "b": "B",
      "back": "Back",
      "browserback": "BrowserBack",
      "browserfavorites": "BrowserFavorites",
      "browserforward": "BrowserForward",
      "browserhome": "BrowserHome",
      "browserrefresh": "BrowserRefresh",
      "browsersearch": "BrowserSearch",
      "browserstop": "BrowserStop",
      "c": "C",
      "cancel": "Cancel",
      "capital": "Capital",
      "capslock": "CapsLock",
      "clear": "Clear",
      "control": "Control",
      "controlkey": "ControlKey",
      "crsel": "Crsel",
      "d": "D",
      "d0": "0",
      "d1": "1",
      "d2": "2",
      "d3": "3",
      "d4": "4",
      "d5": "5",
      "d6": "6",
      "d7": "7",
      "d8": "8",
      "d9": "9",
      "decimal": "Decimal",
      "delete": "Delete",
      "divide": "Divide",
      "down": "Down",
      "e": "E",
      "end": "End",
      "enter": "Enter",
      "eraseeof": "EraseEof",
      "escape": "Escape",
      "execute": "Execute",
      "exsel": "Exsel",
      "f": "F",
      "f1": "F1",
      "f10": "F10",
      "f11": "F11",
      "f12": "F12",
      "f13": "F13",
      "f14": "F14",
      "f15": "F15",
      "f16": "F16",
      "f17": "F17",
      "f18": "F18",
      "f19": "F19",
      "f2": "F2",
      "f20": "F20",
      "f21": "F21",
      "f22": "F22",
      "f23": "F23",
      "f24": "F24",
      "f3": "F3",
      "f4": "F4",
      "f5": "F5",
      "f6": "F6",
      "f7": "F7",
      "f8": "F8",
      "f9": "F9",
      "finalmode": "FinalMode",
      "g": "G",
      "h": "H",
      "hanguelmode": "HanguelMode",
      "hangulmode": "HangulMode",
      "hanjamode": "HanjaMode",
      "help": "Help",
      "home": "Home",
      "i": "I",
      "imeaccept": "IMEAccept",
      "imeaceept": "IMEAceept",
      "imeconvert": "IMEConvert",
      "imemodechange": "IMEModeChange",
      "imenonconvert": "IMENonconvert",
      "insert": "Insert",
      "j": "J",
      "junjamode": "JunjaMode",
      "k": "K",
      "kanamode": "KanaMode",
      "kanjimode": "KanjiMode",
      "keycode": "KeyCode",
      "l": "L",
      "launchapplication1": "LaunchApplication1",
      "launchapplication2": "LaunchApplication2",
      "launchmail": "LaunchMail",
      "lbutton": "Left Mouse",
      "lcontrolkey": "L Control",
      "left": "Left",
      "linefeed": "LineFeed",
      "lmenu": "L Menu",
      "lshiftkey": "L Shift",
      "lwin": "LWin",
      "m": "M",
      "mbutton": "Middle Mouse",
      "medianexttrack": "MediaNextTrack",
      "mediaplaypause": "MediaPlayPause",
      "mediaprevioustrack": "MediaPreviousTrack",
      "mediastop": "MediaStop",
      "menu": "Menu",
      "modifiers": "Modifiers",
      "multiply": "Multiply",
      "n": "N",
      "next": "Next",
      "noname": "NoName",
      "none": "None",
      "numlock": "NumLock",
      "numpad0": "NumPad 0",
      "numpad1": "NumPad 1",
      "numpad2": "NumPad 2",
      "numpad3": "NumPad 3",
      "numpad4": "NumPad 4",
      "numpad5": "NumPad 5",
      "numpad6": "NumPad 6",
      "numpad7": "NumPad 7",
      "numpad8": "NumPad 8",
      "numpad9": "NumPad 9",
      "o": "O",
      "oem1": "1",
      "oem102": "0",
      "oem2": "2",
      "oem3": "3",
      "oem4": "4",
      "oem5": "5",
      "oem6": "6",
      "oem7": "7",
      "oem8": "8",
      "oembackslash": "\\",
      "oemclear": "OemClear",
      "oemclosebrackets": "]",
      "oemcomma": ",",
      "oemminus": "-",
      "oemopenbrackets": "[",
      "oemperiod": ".",
      "oempipe": "|",
      "oemplus": "+",
      "oemquestion": "?",
      "oemquotes": "'",
      "oemsemicolon": "OemSemicolon",
      "oemtilde": "`",
      "p": "P",
      "pa1": "Pa1",
      "packet": "Packet",
      "pagedown": "Page Down",
      "pageup": "Page Up",
      "pause": "Pause",
      "play": "Play",
      "print": "Print",
      "printscreen": "PrintScreen",
      "prior": "Prior",
      "processkey": "ProcessKey",
      "q": "Q",
      "r": "R",
      "rbutton": "Right Mouse",
      "rcontrolkey": "R Control",
      "return": "Return",
      "right": "Right",
      "rmenu": "R Menu",
      "rshiftkey": "R Shift",
      "rwin": "RWin",
      "s": "S",
      "scroll": "Scroll",
      "select": "Select",
      "selectmedia": "SelectMedia",
      "separator": "Separator",
      "shift": "Shift",
      "shiftkey": "ShiftKey",
      "sleep": "Sleep",
      "snapshot": "Snapshot",
      "space": "Space",
      "subtract": "Subtract",
      "t": "T",
      "tab": "Tab",
      "u": "U",
      "up": "Up",
      "v": "V",
      "volumedown": "VolumeDown",
      "volumemute": "VolumeMute",
      "volumeup": "VolumeUp",
      "w": "W",
      "x": "X",
      "xbutton1": "XButton1",
      "xbutton2": "XButton2",
      "y": "Y",
      "z": "Z",
      "zoom": "Zoom"
    }
  },
  "Login": {
    "back": "Back",
    "forgot": "Forgot Password?",
    "login": "Login",
    "password": "Password:",
    "savepass": "Save Password",
    "title": "Login",
    "username": "Username:"
  },
  "Main": {
    "gamename": "Intersect Client"
  },
  "MainMenu": {
    "credits": "Credits",
    "exit": "Exit",
    "login": "Login",
    "options": "Settings",
    "optionstooltip": "",
    "register": "Register",
    "title": "Main Menu"
  },
  "Options": {
    "fps30": "30",
    "fps60": "60",
    "fps90": "90",
    "fps120": "120",
    "apply": "Apply",
    "back": "Back",
    "cancel": "Cancel",
    "fullscreen": "Fullscreen",
    "autoclosewindows": "Auto-close Windows",
    "musicvolume": "Music Volume: {00}%",
    "resolution": "Resolution:",
    "restore": "Restore Defaults",
    "soundvolume": "Sound Volume: {00}%",
    "targetfps": "Target FPS:",
    "title": "Options",
    "unlimitedfps": "No Limit",
    "vsync": "V-Sync"
  },
  "Parties": {
    "inviteprompt": "{00} has invited you to their party. Do you accept?",
    "kick": "Kick {00}",
    "kicklbl": "Kick",
    "leader": "Leader",
    "leadertip": "Party Leader",
    "leave": "Leave Party",
    "leavetip": "Leave Tip",
    "name": "{00} - Lv. {01}",
    "partyinvite": "Party Invite",
    "title": "Party",
    "vital0": "HP:",
    "vital0val": "{00} / {01}",
    "vital1": "MP:",
    "vital1val": "{00} / {01}"
  },
  "QuestLog": {
    "abandon": "Abandon",
    "abandonprompt": "Are you sure that you want to quit the quest \"{00}\"?",
    "abandontitle": "Abandon Quest: {00}",
    "back": "Back",
    "completed": "Quest Completed",
    "currenttask": "Current Task:",
    "inprogress": "Quest In Progress",
    "notstarted": "Quest Not Started",
    "taskitem": "{00}/{01} {02}(s) gathered.",
    "tasknpc": "{00}/{01} {02}(s) slain.",
    "title": "Quest Log"
  },
  "QuestOffer": {
    "accept": "Accept",
    "decline": "Decline",
    "title": "Quest Offer"
  },
  "Regex": {
    "email": "^(([\\w-]+\\.)+[\\w-]+|([a-zA-Z]{1}|[\\w-]{2,}))@((([0-1]?[0-9]{1,2}|25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9])\\.([0-1]?[0-9]{1,2}|25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9])\\.([0-1]?[0-9]{1,2}|25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9])\\.([0-1]?[0-9]{1,2}|25[0-5]|2[0-4][0-9])){1}|([a-zA-Z]+[\\w-]+\\.)+[a-zA-Z]{2,4})$",
    "password": "^[-_=\\+`~!@#\\$%\\^&\\*()\\[\\]{}\\\\|;\\:'\",<\\.>/\\?a-zA-Z0-9]{4,64}$",
    "username": "^[a-zA-Z0-9]{2,20}$"
  },
  "Registration": {
    "back": "Back",
    "confirmpass": "Confirm Password:",
    "email": "Email:",
    "emailinvalid": "Email is invalid.",
    "password": "Password:",
    "passwordmatch": "Passwords didn't match!",
    "register": "Register",
    "title": "Register",
    "username": "Username:"
  },
  "ResetPass": {
    "back": "Cancel",
    "code": "Enter the reset code that was sent to you:",
    "fail": "Error!",
    "failmsg": "The reset code was not valid, has expired, or the account does not exist!",
    "inputcode": "Please enter your password reset code.",
    "password": "New Password:",
    "password2": "Confirm Password:",
    "submit": "Submit",
    "success": "Success!",
    "successmsg": "Your password has been reset!",
    "title": "Password Reset"
  },
  "Resources": {
    "cancelled": "Download was Cancelled!",
    "failedtoload": "Failed to load Resources!",
    "resourceexception": "Failed to download client resources.\\n\\nException Info: {00}\\n\\nWould you like to try again?",
    "resourcesfatal": "Failed to load resources from client directory and Ascension Game Dev server. Cannot launch game!"
  },
  "Server": {
    "statuslabel": "Server Status: {00}",
    "online": "Online",
    "offline": "Offline",
    "failed": "Network Error",
    "connecting": "Connecting...",
    "unknown": "Unknown"
  },
  "Shop": {
    "buyitem": "Buy Item",
    "buyitemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to buy?",
    "cannotsell": "This shop does not accept that item!",
    "costs": "Costs {00} {01}(s)",
    "sellitem": "Sell Item",
    "sellitemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to sell?",
    "sellprompt": "Do you wish to sell the item: {00}?",
    "sellsfor": "Sells for {00} {01}(s)",
    "wontbuy": "Shop Will Not Buy This Item"
  },
  "SpellDesc": {
    "addsymbol": "+",
    "casttime": "Cast Time: {00} Seconds",
    "cooldowntime": "Cooldown: {00} Seconds",
    "desc": "{00}",
    "duration": "Duration: {00}s",
    "effectlist": {
      "0": "",
      "1": "Silences Target",
      "2": "Stuns Target",
      "3": "Snares Target",
      "4": "Blinds Target",
      "5": "Stealths Target",
      "6": "Transforms Target",
      "7": "Cleanses Target",
      "8": "Target becomes Invulnerable",
      "9": "Shields Target",
      "10": "Makes the target fall asleep",
      "11": "Applies an On Hit effect to the target",
      "12": "Taunts Target"
    },
    "effects": "Effects:",
    "prereqs": "Prerequisites:",
    "shield": "Shielding: {00}",
    "radius": "Hit Radius: {00}",
    "removesymbol": "-",
    "spelltypes": {
      "0": "Combat Spell",
      "1": "Warp to Map",
      "2": "Warp to Target",
      "3": "Dash",
      "4": "Special"
    },
    "stats": {
      "0": "Attack: {00}",
      "1": "Ability Power: {00}",
      "2": "Defense: {00}",
      "3": "Magic Resist: {00}",
      "4": "Speed: {00}"
    },
    "targettypes": {
      "0": "Self Cast",
      "1": "Targetted - Range: {00} Tiles",
      "2": "AOE",
      "3": "Projectile - Range: {00} Tiles",
      "4": "On Hit",
      "5": "Trap"
    },
    "vitals": {
      "0": "HP: {00}{01}",
      "1": "MP: {00}{01}"
    },
    "vitalcosts": {
      "0": "HP Cost: {00}",
      "1": "MP Cost: {00}"
    }
  },
  "Spells": {
    "cooldown": "{00}s",
    "forgetspell": "Forget Spell",
    "forgetspellprompt": "Are you sure you want to forget {00}?",
    "title": "Spells"
  },
  "Trading": {
    "accept": "Accept",
    "offeritem": "Offer Item",
    "offeritemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to offer?",
    "pending": "Pending",
    "requestprompt": "{00} has invited you to trade items with them. Do you accept?",
    "revokeitem": "Revoke Item",
    "revokeitemprompt": "How many/much {00} would you like to revoke?",
    "theiroffer": "Their Offer:",
    "title": "Trading with {00}",
    "traderequest": "Trading Invite",
    "value": "Value: {00}",
    "youroffer": "Your Offer:"
  },
  "EscapeMenu": {
    "title": "Menu",
    "options": "Options",
    "characterselect": "Characters",
    "logout": "Logout",
    "exittodesktop": "Desktop",
    "close": "Close"
  },
  "Numbers": {
    "thousands": "k",
    "millions": "m",
    "billions": "b",
    "dec": ".",
    "comma": ","
  }
}